<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ENGL 111 Project 3 on ENGL111 Project 3</title>
    <link>https://engl111.hsiang.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ENGL 111 Project 3 on ENGL111 Project 3</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020-2030, Wen Hsiang Shih and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 06:22:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://engl111.hsiang.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://engl111.hsiang.io/post/reflection-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 06:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engl111.hsiang.io/post/reflection-3/</guid>
      <description>Report In this theme, I would like to reflect on collaboration topic based on my Vlog #8 and project #2 reflection.
Being able to work with others is a vital skill to succeed in the modern society. Nowadays, the problems we are facing are complex to solve by single person. It&amp;rsquo;s important for us to learn collaboration in school before we go to work in industries.
Relate In our project 2, we first had a hard time to determine the topic of the project, and then had some problems figurint out when to start working on the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stereotype &amp; Generalization</title>
      <link>https://engl111.hsiang.io/post/reflection-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 06:21:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engl111.hsiang.io/post/reflection-2/</guid>
      <description>Report For this theme, I select journal #8. My journal #8 is based on a book, Funny in Farsi, a story about the life of an Iranian girl. The book shows how the author has been suffering from the stereotypes of Iranian.
Relate As an international student, it is easy for me to understand from what she suffered, though I have not experienced serious discrimination in the US. It&amp;rsquo;s natural but incorrect that people interact with others based on stereotypes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity</title>
      <link>https://engl111.hsiang.io/post/reflection-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 20:19:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engl111.hsiang.io/post/reflection-1/</guid>
      <description>Selected Material vlog link #1
Reflection Connection </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://engl111.hsiang.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://engl111.hsiang.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Wen-Hsiang, from Purdue Univeristy. My major is Electrical and Computer Engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>